Fowler C. West papers, Inclusive: 1964-2009, Bulk: 1965-1993
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), 1975-1993; 2
  - Speeches and Statements, 1983-1993; 10
    - Meeting on Off-Exchange Issues, 1987 June 9 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Arbitration and CFTC Reparations in Light of McMahon, 10th Annual Commodities Law Institute, 1987 October 15 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Commodity Fraud and the Elderly, 1987 December (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Dissent with Regards to Cox and Fry, circa 1987 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Winter Conference National District Attorneys Association Metropolitan Prosecutors Committee, 1988 February 27 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Before the Futures Industry Association 13th Annual National Futures Industry Conference Workshop: “Managed Money”, 1988 March 10 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Before the South Carolina Department of Consumer Affairs Kickoff Breakfast in Celebration of National Consumers Week/Annual Credit Education Week, 1988 April 25 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Before the Industry Council for Tangible Assets, 1988 April 29 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Senate Committee on Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry, 1988 June 10 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Eleventh Annual Commodities Law Institute, 1988 October 19-21 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - ANPA/CBI Fraud Advertising Seminar, 1988 November 17 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Telemarketing and Investment Fraud Forum, circa 1988 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Proposed Rules for Hybrids, Statutory Interpretation of Hybrids, 1989 Jan 5 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Current Issues of Interest to the “Managed Money” Industry-Before the 14th Annual National Futures Industry Conference, 1989 March 16 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Before the Texas Cotton Association’s 78th Annual Convention, 1989 March 31 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Open Commission Meeting-Quarterly Objectives, 1989 June 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - ABA Conference, What a Difference Three Years Makes, 1989 July 11 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - What A Difference Three Years Makes, 1989 July 14 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Commission Adoption of Final Hybrid Rule, 1989 July 17 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Insider Trading in the Futures Markets, 1989 August 1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - The Chicago Investigation, 1989 August 2 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Commission Meeting-Legislative, 1989 October 6 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - In the Matter of September 1984 Frozen Concentrated Orange Juice Future, 1989 November 22 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Before the Futures Industry Association-Law and Compliance Division, 1989 December 14 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - The Gas Futures Trading Conference, 1990 January 8 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Futures Industry Association-Law and Compliance Division, 1990 January 25 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - The Futures Industry Association Fifteenth Anniversary, The National Futures Industry Conference, 1990 March 9 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - West Proposes Inter-Agency Jurisdictional Arbitration Panel, 1990 March 19 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - International Approaches to the Regulation of Futures, Forwards, Swaps, and Hybrids, 1990 May 2 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - National Grade Trade Council, 1990 May 9 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Meeting of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, 1990 June 20 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Commerce, Consumer and Monetary Affairs Subcommittee of the House Committee on Government Operations Hearing on Telemarketing Fraud, 1990 July 12 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Commodity Futures Trading Commission Before the Valdosta Kiwanis Club, 1990 August 17 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Brent Issue, Committee on Commodities and Futures Law, NY State Bar Association, 1990 Nov 29 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Support on Behalf of NASAA State Commodity Code, circa 1990 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Dissent, circa 1990 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - The Gas Futures Treading Conference, 1991 February 13 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Brent Issue, Chicago Bar Association Commodities Law Committee, 1991 February 15 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - The National Milk Producers Federation 75th Anniversary Annual Meeting, 1991 December 03 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Futures Exchange Operations Program for the Moscow Commodity Exchange, 1992 March 12 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Subcommittee on Conservation, Credit and Rural Development, 1992 May 19 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - National Conference on Telemarketing Fraud: Who are the Victims?, 1992 June 26 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Commodities Law Institute Chicago Kent College of Law, 1992 October 23 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - National Consumers Week Workshop “Operation Wise Buy: Fact Fight Fraud”, 1992 October 29 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Open Commission Meeting on Swaps and Hybrids, 1993 January 14 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - NFA’s Proposed Amendment and Interpretive Notice to its Compliance Rule 2-9, 1993 January 19 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Subjects, 1982-1991; 11
    The Subjects subseries contains all CFTC materials not filed with a particular committee meeting or with correspondence files. It is the largest subseries in the collection and is arranged alphabetically by subject. It includes various materials related to topics such as the audit trail, which allowed regulators to detect fraud and abuse in trading; Brent North Sea Crude Oil contracts, a major issue before the CFTC in the early 1990s; and customer restitution, of which West was a proponent.
    - Agriculture Appropriations Bill, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture in a Global Setting, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture Options, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture Options Expansion, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - AMEX Commodities Corporation, Gold Bullion Contract Applications, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - AMEX Commodities Corporation, Gold Bullion Contract Applications, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - AMEX Commodities Corporation, Gold Bullion Contract Applications, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - AMEX Commodities Corporation, Gold Bullion Contract Applications, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - AMEX Commodities Corporation, Two Year Treasury Note Futures, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Anspacher & Associates, Inc. v. Henderson, et al., 1988 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Anniversary Conference, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Arbitrage, Computerized, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Arbitrage, London, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Arbitration, US Supreme Court, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Arbitration, 1987, 1989, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Association of the Bar of New York Publications, 1987- 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Audit Trail, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Audit Trail, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Audit Trail, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Audit Trail, Agriculture Subcommittee on Conservation, Credit, and Rural Development, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Audit Trail, “CFTC’s Audit Trail Proves the World is Flat,”, 1985 December (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Audit Trail, “CFTC Vows to Push for Tougher Audit Trails,”, 1984 October 22 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Audit Trail, Chronology, 1985 January 17 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Audit Trail, Comments Fowler C. West, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Audit Trail, Commission Meeting, 1984 December 20 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Audit Trail, National Grain and Feed Association, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Audit Trail, John D. Dingell, North American Securities Administration Association, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Audit Trail, Notebook, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Automation to Detect Abuse, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Bank Supervision, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Bankruptcy Rules, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Brody, Alan J., Regulation of Trading of Off-Exchange, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Brady, Nicholas F., 1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Brady, Nicholas F., 1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Brady Commission, Stock Market crash, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, “Forwards vs. Futures: The Great Debate,”, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Brent Market Background Information, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Comment File, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Commission Issuances, 1990 April-June (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, CFTC Policy Interpretations on 15-day Brent Contracts, 1990 June (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Des Moines Register, 1996 April 10 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Dissent by Commissioner Fowler C. West, 1990 September 20 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Federal Case, Correspondence with Court, 1990 April 26 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Federal Case, Court Opinion, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Federal Case, Motions to Dismiss [Denied], 1987 August 18 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Order of the CFTC, “Exemption for Certain Contracts Involving Energy Products”, 1993 April 5 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Report, “U.S. Strategic Petroleum Reserve: Recent Policy Has Increased Costs to Consumers but Not Overall U.S. Energy Security,” U.S. Senate Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations, 2003 March 5 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Brent North Sea Crude Oil Contracts, Speech, “The Brent Issue: More than a Statutory Interpretation”, 1990 November 29 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - American Agriculture Movement, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Briefing Book, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Broker Association, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Buschbaum v. Shearson Lehman Inc Amicus Curie Brief, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Budget Estimate (1986), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Budget Estimate (1989), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Budget Estimate (1990), 1988 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Budget Estimate (1991), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Budget Estimate (1992), 1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Budget Estimate (1993), 1991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Budget Estimate (1994), 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Bush Task Group, Regulation of Financial Services, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Capital News Release, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Capital Markets Competition, Stability, and Fairness Act, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Capital Briefing, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Capital Systems Inc., CFTC Violators, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Carabini, Louis E., Monex International, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Centers for Futures Education, Inc., 1989 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - CFTC and Chicago Board of Trade v. Securities and Exchange Commission/Chicago Board of Options, 1981-1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - CFTC and Lyn Bennett, et al. v. E. F. Hutton Company, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - CFTC and Blunt, et al. v. Hlavinka and Davison, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - CFTC and Krommenhoek v. A-Mark Precious Metals, Inc, et al., 1991 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - CFTC and Cardoza v. CFTC and CBOT, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud, Financial Services Group, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud, First International Commodities Group, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Johanning, Liegberg, Wilkens, Pesek, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Northwest Trading Group, William McCarthy, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Linda Frances Altieri, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Michael J. Lohan, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Philipp Brothers, Inc. et al., 1989 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, A&H Financial Services, Inc., 1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Dunhill Investments, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Alan Horowitz, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Ed Kokes, Mark R. Ilk, GNP Commodities, Inc., 1991 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Bruce Mettelstadt, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Danny L. Scheck, David Zatz, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - CFTC Division of Enforcement, Fraud Case, Michael B. Yatvin, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Dispute with London Brokers, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - CFTC-SEC, Competition Articles, 1983-1985 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - CFTC-SEC, Joint Accords, 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - CFTC-SEC Merger, Articles, 1982-1990 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - CFTC-SEC Merger, Implications, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - CFTC-SEC, Interagency Study, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - CFTC-SEC Reauthorization, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - CFTC v. American Metals Exchange Corp, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Chair, Susan Phillips, 1984-1989 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Aurora, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Canadian Government Bond Futures, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Catastrophe Insurance Futures, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Chairman Testimony, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Chicago Mercantile Exchange Joint Audit Committee, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Corn, 1985,1991 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Disciplinary Action, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, European Currency Bond Futures, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Gold and Silver Futures, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Institutional Futures, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Japanese Government Bond Futures, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Major Market Index Futures, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, MidAmerica Commodity Exchange Affiliation, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Municipal Bond Index, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Oat Futures Contracts, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Options Suit, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Performance Margins, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Persian Gulf War, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Board of Trade Publications, 1978-1988 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Regulation of Off-Exchange Commodity Instruments, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Rule Enforcement, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Rules 353 and 354, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Securities Corporations, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Silver Options, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, Treasury Options, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Board of Trade, UK Gilt Futures, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Futures Markets, Agricultural Futures Delivery Points and Tradeoffs, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, 3 Month Euromark Time Deposit Futures, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Brady Task Force Recommendations, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Crude Oil Futures, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Dollar Index Futures, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Electronic Transaction System, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Eurodollar Options, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, European Exercise Options on Physical Gold, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Federal Funds Rate, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Feeder Cattle Futures, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Global Trading System, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Live Hog Futures, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Morgan Stanley Capital Exchange, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Nikkei Futures Contracts, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Options Clearing Corporation, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, One Month LIBOR Futures, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Physical Gold Options, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Pound-Yen Deutsche Mark Futures, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Publications, 1985-1990 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, S&P Futures and Options, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Simex, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, Swiss Franc and British Pound, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Swap Transactions, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Citizens for a Sound Economy Foundation, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Clearing and Credit Issues, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Coffee Futures and the CFTC, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Coffee, Sugar, and Cocoa Exchange, 1983-1988 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Coffee, Sugar and Cocoa Exchange, Clearing Corporation, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Coffee, Sugar and Cocoa Exchange, Economic Index Futures, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Columbia Futures Center, 1984, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - COMEX, Five Day Silver Options, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Commodity Account Protection, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, Amendments, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, Amendments, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, Board of Trade Clearing Corporation, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, Evaluation of Economic Purpose, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, Forward Contract Exclusion, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, Price Manipulation, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Commodity Exchange Act, US Gulf Coast Jet Fuel Futures, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Commodity Futures Contract, West German Statues and US Commodity Futures, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Commodity Futures Improvement Act, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Commodity Futures Law Reports, Bank Activities, Sale of Precious Metals, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Commodity Futures Prices Manipulation, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Commodities Futures Regulation, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Commodities Futures Trading, Cattle Regulation, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Commodities Law Institute, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Commodity Pool Guidelines, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Commodity Pool Operators, Multi-Advisor and Multi-Investee Pool, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Commodity Pool Operators, Past Performance Records/Expenses, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Commodity Pool Operators, Performance Records, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Commodity Pool Operators, Proposed Regulations, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Commodity Pool Operators, Study, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Commodity Violators Bulletin, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Customer Protection, Cases, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Customer Protection, Reduction in Consumer Protection Memos, 1992 March (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Customer Protection, Testimony, 1992 May 19 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Customer Restitution, Illustrations, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Customer Restitution, Program Implementation, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Customer Restitution, CFTC Press Release, Court Cases, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Customer Restitution, Data FY 1988 Customer Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Customer Restitution, Litigation Assignments, 1989 October (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Customer Restitution, Cases, Conti Commodity Services, Inc., 1991 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Customer Restitution, Cases, Creative Artists Institute v. Smith, Bainey, Harris, Upham and Co., 1986 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Customer Restitution, Cases, Eda s. Cook v. Money International, LTD., 1986 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Customer Restitution, Cases, Edward A. Cox, Tr. And George F. Frey, Jr., 1987 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Customer Restitution, Cases, Equal Opportunity Complaint of Lottie Cohen, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Customer Restitution, Cases, Esther Edwards v. Gerald Inc., 1993 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Customer Restitution, Cases, John W. Bunch v. First Commodity Corporation of Bootan, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Customer Restitution, Cases, Kansas City Board of Trade and William R. Davis, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Customer Restitution, Correspondence, Geoffrey Aronow, Director, CFTC Division of Enforcement, 1996 April (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Customer Restitution, Correspondence, Arthur L. Shipe, U.S. Administrative Law Judge, 1989 October 4 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Customer Restitution, Legislation, American Bar Association, Uniform Crime Victims Reparations Act, Professor Paul Rothstein, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Customer Restitution, Legislation, Andrea M. Corcoran, Director, Division of Trading and Markets, 1989 March (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Customer Restitution, Legislation, Commodities Exchange Act, Amendments, 1989 October (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Customer Restitution, Legislation, Commodities Exchange Act, Final Version in Law, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Customer Restitution, Legislation, Formulating Restitution Proposals, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Customer Restitution, Legislation, Recommendations, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Customer Restitution, Legislation, Restitution Measure Defeated, 1989 October 5-6 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Customer Restitution, Legislation, Securities Law Enforcement Remedies Act, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Dispute Resolution Between Investors, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Division of Economics and Education, Commodity Futures and Options Contracts Specifications, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Division of Trades and Market, Rules and Regulations, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Drought Policy Committee, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Dual Trading Study, 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Dual Trading Restrictions, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Employee Financial Disclosure, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Energy and Commerce Committee Amendments, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Enforcement, Budget Briefing, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Enforcement, Investment Fraud, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Enforcement Systems, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Eurodollar Futures, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - European Community and US Competitiveness, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Exchanges of Futures for Physicals, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Expiration Day Effects, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Export Embargo, Futures Market Hedgers, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Futures Commission Merchant, Disclosure Requirements, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Futures Commission Merchant, Federal Power Marketing Agency, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Federal Reserve, Margin Study, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Federal Reserve, Margin Study, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Federal Reserve, Regulation Y, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Federal Reserve, Alan Greenspan, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Federal Reserve, Earlier Fedwire Opening, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Federal Trade Commission, Barry J. Cutler, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Fiduciary Duty, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Financial Instruments, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Financial Markets Working Group Report, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Financial Planners Registration in New York, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 14)